import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

class Global {
  static int index = 0;
  static int amt = 500;
}

List<Map> questions = [
  {
    "question":
        """In the Film "OMG Oh My God" Kanji Bhai filed a case against whom for the damage of his shop due to an earth quake ?""",
    "op1": "Bharat Mata",
    "op2": "Parliament",
    "op3": "Mumbai City",
    "op4": "Bhagwan",
    "ans": "Bhagwan",
    "color": Colors.purple,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What is the new name of the Hyderabad franchise that would replace Deccan Charges in IPL6 ?",
    "op1": "Sun Chargers",
    "op2": "Nizam Jyothi",
    "op3": "Andhra Aces",
    "op4": "Sun riser Hyderabad",
    "ans": "Sun riser Hyderabad",
    "color": Colors.blue,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "In India,under which Union Misitry does the 'Rajbhasha Vibhag' function ?",
    "op1": "Home Affairs",
    "op2": "HRD",
    "op3": "Culture",
    "op4": "Law & Justice",
    "ans": "Home Affairs",
    "color": Colors.red,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "According to a proverb, what is said to be 'the mother of invention' ?",
    "op1": "Society",
    "op2": "Problem",
    "op3": "Science",
    "op4": "Necessity",
    "ans": "Necessity",
    "color": Colors.yellow,
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actress got married to Siddharth Roy Kapur in 2012 ?",
    "op1": "Prachi Desai",
    "op2": "Lisa Ray",
    "op3": "Vidya Balan",
    "op4": "Sushmita Sen",
    "ans": "Vidya Balan",
    "color": Colors.green,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "To whom did Ravindranath Tagore dedicate his book 'visva parichay' written on science ?",
    "op1": "C v raman",
    "op2": "Satyendta nath Bose",
    "op3": "P c Royn",
    "op4": "Jagdish Chandra Bose",
    "ans": "Satyendta nath Bose",
    "color": Colors.lightBlueAccent,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which of these is a chemical element present in the periodic table ?",
    "op1": "Eurocium",
    "op2": "Asiacium",
    "op3": "Americium",
    "op4": "Africium",
    "ans": "Americium",
    "color": Colors.redAccent,
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not a work of kalidas ?",
    "op1": "Raghuvamsham",
    "op2": "Kadambari",
    "op3": "Vikramorvasiyam",
    "op4": "Meghadutam",
    "ans": "Kadambari",
    "color": Colors.deepPurpleAccent,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "According to the Devi, Bhagavata, from the tears of which god is the rudraksha tree believed to have been created ?",
    "op1": "Vishnu",
    "op2": "Shiva",
    "op3": "Krishna",
    "op4": "Kamadeva",
    "ans": "Shiva",
    "color": Colors.blue,
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these names means ' gold-like' ?",
    "op1": "Sonakshi",
    "op2": "Deepika",
    "op3": "Sonam",
    "op4": "Katrina",
    "ans": "Sonam",
    "color": Colors.orangeAccent,
  },
];
